Actually. Yes
.
Amazing mind, brilliant mind. Well done, Mordanasan.
So, so, Mohammed, I'm not sure who else is in here. I messaged our Seema. She's going to join shortly. I see Indra is here, so maybe we can get started because we're almost half an hour late.
Absolutely, I'm so sorry, Indra. I'm so sorry. Please go ahead.
Yeah.
Ash.
I have no idea.
Everyone, sorry for being late. I just arrived
I'm sorry, Ash, can you… okay, yeah, I'm sorry, it was…
No, sir.
Okay.
I
I had a work meeting, but
Okay, everyone.
I think we can definitely start
I see that we have
At least
Two new buddies with us, is that…
Right? Two new members.
Krishna, and…
Caballon or
I don't know where… how to pronounce it, but… and I know that
Presented yourself, I think
In multimodal, maybe?
Because I know you've presented yourself. I
I just don't remember where
But I don't think… I think this is your first backend meeting, right?
Or not
Okay.
Right.
Ah, this is my first backend meeting, but I have already attended the technical meetings.
That was it, okay. So great, you…
We're already presented for everyone. The other two new members, did you guys present yourself to the team already?
If not, you guys can do it now. Just tell us where you're from, and if what's your academic and work experience
Do you want me to start?
Sure, you can
Sir, you can hear me, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, hello, I'm Muhammad Kabbalan, but
To not make Muhammad sad, I will be… I will call myself Mr. Kavalan
Okay.
I recently graduated, I have a bachelor degree
Computer science.
I used to be a front-end developer, but
This year I began my journey at Backend because I found it also interesting to
See, we… the work behind the scenes
And
My current stock, now I'm just using Node Express with MongoDB. I have familiarity with SQL, Firebase
But my current focus now is on Node Express with MongoDB
Okay.
Welcome to the team. Here, we are using for the backend Python with
Jungle, and we use
multiple kinds of database, so you'll have fun with that.
Yeah.
Great. Welcome to the team.
Thank you.
Kishna?
Hi, hello everyone, I'm Krishna, and
I'm audible
Yeah, I can hear you. It's a bit low, but I can hear you.
Okay.
I am Krishna, and I'm in my final year of engineering, and I'm doing computer engineering
And it's my first internship
Awesome.
Welcome to the team, Krishna. Have you already in the other internships were on Backend as well?
No, actually.
But I have done projects, like, in space and other things, but it's my first time in Backend.
Awesome.
Great.
I don't know, Devu, if you want to introduce yourself again, just for this lot here.
Yeah, sure, sure, sure. So, hi guys, my name is Koshik. So, I have graduated this year from VITAP in a stream of computer science engineering, so I have a…
Prior knowledge in, ah, flask jungle every, ah, and REST APIs and my main part is developing Python development and artificial intelligence through LLMs and RAGs. So I have built…
I have worked on few projects, uh, one of them were AI assistant Pro, which helps you like, which helps the
HR through the resume. If you ask a question, it will go through the resume and it will
Provide you the answer. So, it was based on RAG pipelines and LLMs, which I use, the framework which I used was LangChain. And one more project was Lemonleaf disease detection, where I used deep learning model and OpenCV. And I have achieved 98 percentage validity accuracy.
So now I'm currently working for Flow Labs, where I am in the back end team. That's it.
Awesome. Welcome to the team.
So…
Well, I think
I forgot for
Every other time, but I think I should present myself as well. I'm Indra, and I'm from Brazil
I am a computer engineer. I graduated three years ago, actually, and I've been in Flo Labs for
Almost one year, but I've been since the end of last year, and
I am the team lead here for the Backend team, the front-end team, and the multimodal team
And I also worked as embedded software developer for the humanoid team.
Here in the Backend team, we
Focus more on the FloBrain Backend, but we also
We also work with the AI travel agent Backend
or some other backends if we need it to. The front-end team has a more broad work. For example, they will start on the CAIPO app right now
So they also do that. But our focus here is the FloBrain. So, I will share my screen for you guys to take a look at our
project page on Notion
So
Here is the FloBrain project page. Currently, we are starting the version two, but for version 1, you can find all the documents
created throughout the development and
the management for it
And it basically
settles down what is the Flo brain as an overall
Project.
But for version 2, we'll be focusing more on the dashboard of FloBrain. So, we have a
Website in future… in the future, we have a mobile app. For the dashboard of FloBrain, that's more
Directed to
The company members, things like that, but you can also have personal use, so that's what we'll be focusing on version 2. But we still need to finish some details for version 1, so that's what you guys
We'll focus right now. So this is the overview tab. You'll find all the documents here. Then, on the Tasks tab, you'll find all the tasks that we're working on. What I like to do is filter by
So each task is labeled with Backend or front-end, so that's easy to find. And then for
The new members. What I ask you guys to do is
I created a task for each of you
And it basically has the links of the PRD and the Documentation Hub
It's the foundation of the Flo brain. And then the repository link. So you guys can clone the repository. It's a mono repository. So it's for everything related to FloBrain except the multimodal. So it has the front end of FloBrain and the Backend.
So
You guys will need to clone it after reading the documentation. Clone it, read the readme file where it states explains a little bit more about the code structure in itself, and then try to run the system in your computer
Inside the GitHub repository, it has the FloBrain Core folder, and that's where it is in the backend system.
So, I assigned the three of you this desk. Each desk is for each of you. The only thing I got a problem is for Krishna's, because
I cannot
Find it… find your Notion
user
Is your user… in another format? Or
It's not your name, or is it…
Are you on our username?
It's, crucial
Can you send me here in the chat, then I can help you.
Oh
Okay.
With that finished, now I want to hear from
Our
Well, first of all, did you guys understand how it's working right now? You get a better feel of it once you start taking a look at the documentation
Running the project, but
Do you guys have any questions for now?
Okay, I'll take this as a note.
Everything is clear
Okay, awesome. Then I want to hear from Peter
How was your project onboarding? Were you able to read all the documentation? I know you also had the front end one, but
Were you able to clone the repository and run it?
I guess I read the documentations, and I cloned the repo.
But I cannot open for front end because I don't have the account information, username and password.
So I just saw everything from outside.
when running the FloBrain app, you mean? The site
Yes, yes.
You can create your own user
We don't have a validation just for company users, so anyone can create
Okay, great.
So
Okay, do you have any questions about the architecture or something like that?
Uh, no, I'm right now doing my master classes, but I won't know when I'm able to get some tasks. Is it after finishing all my master classes or how it's working?
No, I'll already give you tasks, don't worry about it.
Great, thank you, Peter.
Who else was doing their project onboarding
We had Nitesh, but I think
It's not here
Ash, were you doing yours? Right?
Let me see if you already put it on time
Yes
Okay,
was
Do you have any questions about it, or were you able to understand it, run it
I did Janet, I read the documentation
Some of it, not all of it, so I'm… like, I have an overall idea of the system.
Okay.
Great. What about you, Shuaibi? Were you able to do it as well? I see it's been done here
Yes, I've been able to, complete my
projects have already called the F1. That was my masterclasses.
Awesome. Do you have any questions about the project?
No, not really, no illi.
Okay.
Great, thank you. Then, let's go to
Some of the tasks we had
This one that we
Had to fix some information that we're sending through the APIs, because they were just mocked information, since when we created those APIs, we didn't have the whole system integrated yet
But once we had the whole system, we needed to go back and send the real information. That's done. The pull request is merged, so
That's it with that.
For creating the AI models table
I also reviewed the pull request, so that's also done.
Then
Let me see who's here
Okay, so our semi is in here, neither is Lucas. So for their task, which was merge the AWS containers, they were finishing that off. I'll ask them
Through Discord
Is it going
And then we have
Money's
And washings task about validating memory implementation.
Awesome. Neither of them are here, so I won't be able to have an update right now.
Something that we all as a team need to do is we currently have a documentation
Multiple documentations about the flow rate system, and it's a documentation more towards developers in itself
So we want to actually
Have the same documentation, but in a more
In a better language for the public and the users that will use FloBrain and want to
contribute for flow brain development, things like that. So this is our current… this here, for example, is just for development, so this is the roadmap for developing version 1, things like that.
But
This here explains a little bit more how the FloBrain website is divided into
the interface, and then the backend
So
And then we have the documentation hub, which states the
Architecture of the front end, and then the architecture of the backend
So what we need to do to create this public documentation is we need to go through the
Current documentation and create a new one, with a more accessible language and possible with more
Maybe animations, things like that, that has a more visual effect for the public. So
I will give this, actually, to the new incomes, because you guys will
need to read the documentation already. So
Then you guys can
do that, and also help us create the new documentation.
So… here
And then
And…
Okay
Oh, I'll show
How do you spell your name, Ash?
Because I don't think it's ash in ocean.
Awesome
Okay, thank you.
His name is Ahsan, Ash is abbreviation.
It's excellent
AHSN
-Oh.
Dammit. Okay
And… let me see if I'm missing…
Okay.
I still can't find your
Thank you, sir
Krishna
Actually, that evening is my AIRS01.
Okay.
Because if I take
It also doesn't appear. Okay.
Oh, actually, that mail is my… you can search by mail, AIRS01.
Oh, check it out later. Okay, so you guys can start working on that, and then for
And I think, first of all
Let me stop sharing my screen
I want to hear a little bit from Rawa, since it's been a long time no see. How are you doing?
Good. How is your availability right now?
I'm doing good, Andrew, I hope about you?
Uh, I think I'm okay to do rocks now. I can work on tests.
Okay, awesome. So, I think you can
Join
The new incomes on creating the documentation
And then…
I think the only one that would be missing
A task would be you write off on
Yes.
Yeah, I think you can join money in Washing for validating memory implementation
So we can actually finish that chapter and move to the version two of FloBrain
Is that okay for you
Yeah, that… that's okay.
Okay, awesome. Thank you, Ivan.
So let me add Rawa to
The task
And then
Okay, and often children, the memory task.
Okay, so for now, that's it for the FloBrain. Now
Just… does anyone want to add anything else for FloBrain
Okay.
Now, I think
I want to ask this.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, for this project or this task specifically, should we do it together, like as a teamwork or each one of us doing his work?
Great question.
After review, you are choosing one.
Let's try to do as a team. So, I will create a
file on Notion, and then everyone can collaborate on that
Okay, perfect. Thank you.
Thank you for the question, Peter.
Okay, so for you guys to
Also
Know about the AI travel agent. This is
I think everyone here already know what kind of what
But here is our page on Notion for the AI travel agent project
Here in the overview, you can find a little summary about the project and then the front-end repository, Backend repository
maybe I'll have to
Update, but I am
I wasn't the team lead to create the project. We are just trying to maintain it right now. So our current
biggest problem that we're having is that
The Backend deployment that was working in the past was
taken down, so we have to get it back up again. And that's what Arcemma and RSMA is doing, and then OFAN is also
Doing that with Ursama, but trying to
See if the Backend is actually working. Were you able to
Run
and review the backend
code to see if there is anything breaking that we shouldn't
Deploy open
I… I did that, but… that was the last time I was working on the app
But, the current
of this last and my deals gave to me was
She has some issues trying to deploy on AWS
Okay.
So, I have to, like, look through the error and see how
No
Yeah, that's the current update
Okay, that's, great progress, at least. Thank you so much, Ofhan.
So, that's what we're trying to fix right now, is that get the backend back up again in AWS, and then
the website will be fully working again. In the future, when we finish this version 1 of FloBrain and has some progress for version two, we want to migrate
The
Not actually my great, but there are some details for the AI travel agent, the agent in itself, we want to
have the prompt enhancement and all of that into the multimodal, and then connect the front end with FloBrain Backend, because it will
have the same system
So that's what we're gonna try to do in the future.
Yeah, I think that's it also for the AI travel agent, and those are the two projects we're, sorry, Ash, I didn't see you were with your
Hand raised. Do you want to say something?
I just wanted to say, can I help out in the deployment? Like, it's… I do not have experience in DevOps
But it's something I really look forward to looking, so if I can help
Like, doing the… with ice cream
Definitely, I will
Add you to the task, and you can talk with Ofun and RSMA to
help out.
Thank you for that.
Okay, and…
I just also wanted to let you know that I have a background in software engineering
And, like, I have a lot of experience in SRS documentation
So, like, if you need help there
Requirements, use cases, or anything like that, I can help out there too.
That's great, Ash. Thank you so much. I'll definitely ask for your help.
Thank you.
Anyone else want to
Ask any questions, comment
Or anything?
You know, yeah, if you could mute yourself because we hear something in the background.
Yeah, if nobody else has any, uh, anything they want to say, I do want to mention.
Yeah, a couple things in the front-end dev meeting, uh, about the typo mobile app.
We did some research during in the meeting.
On ChatGPT, looking at the competitors and we came to the email was one of the competitors. They're open source. They have an open source dev kit, and…
Their mobile app is MIT licensed. That means it can be used for commercial purposes. They're pretty advanced.
So, yeah, we… they have their access to GitHub, and so what we decided is the path we want to go down is to use their mobile app.
So… it's already…
It's already developed with a lot of functionality, let's say, and stuff that we need.
So anyway, I posted in the front end dev team and also just down the IoT team.
Um, the research, which has a link to their GitHub and their website, I guess.
So yeah, I just wanted to mention that. And in that same breath, um,
Our model is…
to…
On the… on… in FlowBrain,
To use as much open source software as possible.
We're an open source, open science, open community, open building company, organization, or building in the open.
And, um,
And so on the back end, things that we want to integrate.
We've got an open source CRM we've researched is the top one on GitHub. We want to integrate. We want to move away from HubSpot, but we want to integrate that into Flowbrain.
Um, we have Life Kit. It's an open source platform for video calls, chats, um…
Similar to, like, say, Discord, I'm not sure, maybe Discord is using it also. Uh, where you can do rooms, and have, like, Zoom calls, so that's one of our integrations. We have another integration for…
Time tracking, similar to toggle moving to Flowbrain as our time tracking tool. There's an open source module.
And there's one other one, uh, I can't remember which one it is that we're looking at integrating, so…
Yeah, I wanted to find out where… where are we on, kind of, Andrew, we talked about, like, at least taking three of them and doing them all at the same time so we can kind of identify and learn. Wuxing came to the meeting yesterday, but
Uh, he's… he has exams, so his availability is going to be very limited for the next 30 days.
Uh, and Manny just sent a message earlier, he had something came up, and he has to travel out of town for a week, so he… he's gone for a week. Wuxian's gone for a week, and… and so how do we move this… those integrations forward to plug those into into
Yeah.
Currently, we need to focus on finishing the memory so we can
Move that forward since the ones we have that are
They have knowledge on memory is many in washing because they were here since memory was being implemented. So
they will already be working with that. But
Once
The
New members are… understands our architecture, things like that. Then we can start working on
Implementing the features for version 2.
Flow brain.
Okay, so are those apps, those backend…
Those are part of version 2.
Those open source apps that I mentioned.
Yeah, because version two will have time tracking Notion tasks, things like that. So that
We'll come to that
Okay, um…
So yeah, I'm just, is there something we can do?
Yeah, as far as, like, setting a task for people to research those specific open source.
Uh, platforms, and start looking at, like… so, once they're done, the documentation is being worked on, we've got those apps that we're going to integrate, and then, you know, how do we hit the ground running? Because we've got these open source, very advanced
tools that a lot of people are using. We've got AI to we've got our front end, the UI kind of what it, you know, okay, kind of there a little bit.
And then we're all hopefully everyone's taking their Anthropic, got their Anthropic certificate as part of the masterclass.
And, um, you know, our capabilities now with the new versions of Anthropic and ChatGPT that just came out that are much better at coding, it really should like
You know, like, amplify us executing and getting, you know, Flowbrain, you know, working with a lot of features and functionality that normally would take years to develop.
I want to try to understand, like, you know, the path that we're gonna go down, and how quickly can we realistically, you know,
Launch those things…
There are a few things that need to be done. They can be done in parallel, but there are a few things that need to be released before those specifically features
But yeah, as soon as we get everyone acquainted to the code architecture and things like that.
Then
They will start to develop it.
Okay, okay. And…
So… so…
I guess by next week, all that's going to be done as far as getting…
Understand the architecture.
Okay.
Yeah, I hope so. Now it depends for everyone here to be able to do that. But yeah, that's the goal
Okay, okay, that sounds great. So, yeah, I'm looking forward to moving that forward.
Yeah, me too.
Looking forward to moving that forward.
Yeah.
Okay, awesome, awesome. Thank you.
Okay, anything else?
Nope. Okay, so that was it for us today, everyone.
Yeah, we're currently focusing on finishing version one of FloBrain and then we can
Start off version 2, and also keep going with maintaining AI travel agent.
So, thank you so much for the meeting, guys. I hope to see you all on the next possible meetings that work together or on Sunday.
Hi, everyone. Thank you.
Have a great week, everyone.
Touch